Before we get started here, I'm actually
going to bring in somebody that knows
you a little bit better than I do to to
help us out. Mom.
Hey, Mike.
>> So, there some questions I'm going to
ask you. Has it set in that you're a
Detroit Lion yet?
>> Yeah, it's definitely began to set in a
little bit. Um, it's a it's a surreal
moment really, but you know, being here,
being able to see everything, you know,
tour the facility, meet everyone, it's
it's been incredible. It's it's really
starting to set in. What are your
impressions being in the building as a
lion for the first time?
>> Obviously, you know, the facility is
incredible. Very impressive. You know,
all the the weight room, the training
room, the indoor, the meeting rooms,
like everything is is beautiful,
top-notch. You know, just meeting
everyone here. You can you can see the
the fire everyone has in their eyes and,
you know, the determination that
everyone has. It's truly throughout the
whole staff and it's it's awesome.
>> What does a successful first season look
like to you? I'd say for me a successful
first season is earning the trust and
respect of my teammates and coaches.
Whatever role I'm called to be in, if
I'm a guy that my teammates trust when I
run out there and you know they're not
looking to me come critical situations,
they know I'm going to get my job done.
I feel like I'll have been successful in
my first year.
>> When you look back later in your NFL
career, what do you never want to forget
about last night in being drafted? say
the looks on everyone's faces around me,
you know, just just seeing the happiness
and the surprise and the excitement in
everyone else's eyes like that. I don't
know that that really it brings a smile
to my face to to think back to that
moment. So, I'll cherish that memory.
>> What final message would you like to
send to Lions fans about who you are and
your excitement to play in Detroit?
>> Over the moon to to play in Detroit. You
know, Coach Campbell here has built an
amazing culture and I just, you know,
really want to uphold his his standards
and his, you know, tenants that he set
for this team and be a a finisher, be be
a guy who has grit, be a guy who's
physical. I want a team after they get
done playing us to walk off the field
and know that they just played the
Detroit Lions.
>> Very good. And I just wanted to say how
incredibly proud I am of you and uh you
have come so far for I remember dropping
you off at Clemson and to see what you
are today. It's just been amazing. So
congratulations.
>> Thanks mom.
>> You guys want to go?
>> I love your baby. I love you too.
Congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> Mom's tired.